{
    "subject": "resource/Ivesia_pickeringii",
    "predicate": "property/familia",
    "object": "resource/Rosaceae",
    "human_readable": "Ivesia pickeringii is a member of the Rosaceae family.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9508470892906189,
            "question": "Is Ivesia pickeringii a type of rose?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9417569637298584,
            "question": "To which plant family does Ivesia pickeringii belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.670560359954834,
            "question": "What is the scientific name for Ivesia pickeringii?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6379181742668152,
            "question": "What is the ecological role of Ivesia pickeringii?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6200299263000488,
            "question": "Where does Ivesia pickeringii typically grow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48957669734954834,
            "question": "How does Ivesia pickeringii contribute to its ecosystem?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45974239706993103,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of the Rosaceae family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45955315232276917,
            "question": "What are some uses for plants in the Rosaceae family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40847739577293396,
            "question": "Are there any other well-known plants within the Rosaceae family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4034267067909241,
            "question": "Are there any conservation concerns regarding Ivesia pickeringii?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ivesia pickeringii is a member of the Rosaceae family.",
            "html": "dbpedia_575_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other well-known plants within the Rosaceae family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_575_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some uses for plants in the Rosaceae family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_575_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some characteristics of the Rosaceae family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_575_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_575_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_575_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_575_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_575_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_575_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_575_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_575_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_575_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_575_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_575_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the taxonomic classification of \"Ivesia pickeringii\", including that it belongs to the family Rosaceae, which confirms the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}